https://www.simpsonfineart.com/privacy-policy?osCsid=1nnvv4j9qggi9s70qhq1b8nue2

Privacy Policy
Your currency:
My Cart
: 0 item(s)
HomeAll Prints ShopOriginal Paintings About Us E-MailBrowse by Region
Home
Print Galleries
All Art Prints (320)
Scotland by Region (304)
Aberdeen & Grampian (2)
Argyll, The Isles, Loch Lomond, Stirling & The Trossachs (44)
Ayrshire, Arran, Dumfries & Galloway (12)
Fife (19)
Greater Glasgow & Clyde Valley (120)
Highlands Of Scotland (39)
Lothian & Borders (50)
Orkney & Shetland (1)
Perthshire (9)
Tayside (3)
Western Isles (5)
Best selling Artwork (81)
Glasgow Prints (80)
Scottish Sunsets & Sunrises (16)
Edinburgh Prints (36)
Scottish Castles (40)
Golf Courses (17)
Scottish Highlands (44)
Scottish Isles (28)
Churches & Monuments (45)
Scotland's Lochs & Rivers (43)
Scottish Hotels (15)
Scotland's Coastline (33)
Towns & Villages of Scotland (54)
Artists
Jamie Simpson (122)
Jim Simpson (195)
Home»Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis web site is owned by Simpson Fine Art, based in Glasgow, Scotland.Simpson Fine Art does not collect any personal information about you, except that which you knowingly supply to us. We are committed to ensuring the privacy of your personal information and will not sell or pass on your information to any other organisation.1. What information do we collect?a) Personal information you provide such as name and e-mail address etc. We collect this information in connection with specific activities, such as your purchase of prints and email newsletter subscriptions etc.b) Non-personal information. Like other web servers, ours automatically collects data such as IP address (the location of the computer on the internet) and pages viewed. This helps us to determine how many people use our site and which pages are popular. This information does not tell us who you are, it simply allows us to monitor and improve our service.2. Where will the information be held?Personal information submitted through the forms on this site is held only in our computer systems. We promise that we will not share the information you give to us with any other organisation.3. Your right to access the informationYou can ask us at any time for a copy of the personal information that we hold about you. You can also request that we correct or delete the personal information about you that we hold.4. External links There are links on this web site that take you to other web sites outside of our service. These third party web sites are beyond our control, and we do not endorse or accept responsibility for them.5. If you have any further questions, please contact us.Continue
SimpsonFineArt.com is the online gallery of paintings and prints by Scottish artists Jim & Jamie Simpson.
Secure ShoppingShipping & ReturnsCustomer ServiceConditions of Use
My account
Sign inView CartMy account
Follow Us :
Copyright © 2020 Holbi eCommerce development by Holbi
Payment method
